const LiteratureQuestions = [
    {
        question: "Who is the author of the famous literary work 'Rubaiyat'?",
        options: ["Omar Khayyam (عمر خیام)", "Rumi (مولانا روم)", "Ibn Sina (ابن سینا)", "Al-Ghazali (الغزالی)"],
        correct_option: "Omar Khayyam (عمر خیام)"
    },
    {
        question: "Which Islamic scholar is known for his philosophical works such as 'The Incoherence of the Philosophers'?",
        options: ["Al-Farabi (الفارابی)", "Ibn Rushd (ابن رشد)", "Al-Ghazali (الغزالی)", "Ibn Khaldun (ابن خلدون)"],
        correct_option: "Al-Ghazali (الغزالی)"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is considered one of the greatest poets in Persian literature and authored 'Masnavi'?",
        options: ["Rumi (مولانا روم)", "Hafez (خواجه شمس‌الدین محمد حافظ شیرازی)", "Saadi Shirazi (شیخ موسی الدین سعدی شیرازی)", "Omar Khayyam (عمر خیام)"],
        correct_option: "Rumi (مولانا روم)"
    },
    {
        question: "Which Islamic scholar is known for his compilation of 'Arabic Literature'?",
        options: ["Al-Farabi (الفارابی)", "Ibn Rushd (ابن رشد)", "Ibn Khaldun (ابن خلدون)", "Al-Jahiz (الجاحظ)"],
        correct_option: "Al-Jahiz (الجاحظ)"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is known as the 'Prince of Poets' and authored 'Diwan'?",
        options: ["Al-Mutanabbi (المتنبی)", "Ibn Arabi (ابن عربی)", "Ibn Hazm (ابن حزم)", "Al-Bukhari (البخاری)"],
        correct_option: "Al-Mutanabbi (المتنبی)"
    },
    {
        question: "Which Islamic scholar is known for his work 'The Ring of the Dove'?",
        options: ["Ibn Sina (ابن سینا)", "Ibn Rushd (ابن رشد)", "Al-Ghazali (الغزالی)", "Ibn Hazm (ابن حزم)"],
        correct_option: "Ibn Hazm (ابن حزم)"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is known for his philosophical work 'The Incoherence of the Incoherence'?",
        options: ["Al-Farabi (الفارابی)", "Ibn Rushd (ابن رشد)", "Ibn Khaldun (ابن خلدون)", "Ibn Sina (ابن سینا)"],
        correct_option: "Ibn Rushd (ابن رشد)"
    },
    {
        question: "Which Islamic scholar is known for his work 'The Muqaddimah'?",
        options: ["Al-Farabi (الفارابی)", "Ibn Rushd (ابن رشد)", "Ibn Khaldun (ابن خلدون)", "Al-Jahiz (الجاحظ)"],
        correct_option: "Ibn Khaldun (ابن خلدون)"
    },
    {
        question: "Who authored the famous Arabic epic 'Antar bin Shaddad'?",
        options: ["Al-Farabi (الفارابی)", "Al-Jahiz (الجاحظ)", "Al-Asma'i (الأصمعي)", "Ibn Arabi (ابن عربی)"],
        correct_option: "Al-Asma'i (الأصمعي)"
    },
    {
        question: "Which Islamic scholar is known for his work 'Book of Misers'?",
        options: ["Al-Farabi (الفارابی)", "Ibn Rushd (ابن رشد)", "Ibn Khaldun (ابن خلدون)", "Al-Jahiz (الجاحظ)"],
        correct_option: "Al-Jahiz (الجاحظ)"
    }
];

export default LiteratureQuestions;
